<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eagle Eye Systems</title>
    <link>/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eagle Eye Systems</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2016, Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited; All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-us&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;raison-d-être&#34;&gt;Raison d&amp;rsquo;être&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No cyber security firm in Hong Kong provides our methodology to comprehensively assess a company’s IT security defences, despite the threat of cyber attacks having emerged worldwide with speed and ferocity. Hence, we’re here to give you peace of mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-mission&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To bolster the cyber security defences of all types of businesses and recommend solutions to mitigate the risk of being hacked, resulting in the theft of confidential data, damage to reputation and financial losses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-team&#34;&gt;Our Team&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team of experts deliver cost-effective solutions with over 20 years of experience, specializing in cyber security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;next-dimension-of-security-defences&#34;&gt;Next Dimension of Security Defences&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IT security threats are sophisticated, cunning and everyone is a target not just high profile businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So far when businesses typically think of an attack, they think about how much time they are going to be knocked off line. And the clean-up cost—whether it’s technical or legal,” said Peter Singer, author of “Cybersecurity and Cyberwar,” and senior fellow at New America Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was speaking in an interview with Bloomberg News in December 2014, to discuss the multi-million dollar attack on Sony Pictures that exposed the personal information of tens of thousands of people. Since this interview, “Sony Hacked: Three Lessons Learned for Corporations,” was released the situation has remained much the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hackers realize that many companies are restrained by IT security costs spinning out of control, presenting an opportunity for hackers to target any business with financial assets, high risk data or confidential information that can be exploited. The hackers seek anonymity and fame by exposing weaknesses in IT Security &amp;amp; Risk Mitigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No cyber security firm in Hong Kong provides our Baseline Methodology Assessment &amp;amp; Audit to comprehensively assess Information Security Maturity by examining a company’s cyber security defences, and recommends improvements and solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assessment is supported by Penetration Tests to probe a computer system, IT network or Web applications to identify vulnerabilities that a hacker could exploit to launch a cyber attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the event of a business being hacked, our cyber security experts are on call &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; to provide immediate Security Incident Response, as well as monitor a business’s Information Technology assets &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; via our Security and Network Operations Centre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CEO Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd, Sunil Rathour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;binary-face1024x768.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;experts-urge-enterprises-to-tighten-cyber-security-before-hack-not-focus-on-clean-up-job-afterwards&#34;&gt;Experts urge enterprises to tighten cyber security before hack, not focus on clean-up job afterwards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Organisations are being urged to address IT security issues, and abandon the traditional standpoint of waiting to be hacked before they act, to save money in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So far when businesses typically think of an attack, they think about how much time they are going to be knocked off line. And the clean-up cost whether it’s technical or legal,” said Author of “Cybersecurity and Cyberwar” and Senior Fellow at New America Foundation, Peter Singer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What we are seeing from Sony is that all sorts of other costs kick in. Everything from impact on your brand to customers being upset with you and your business partners,” said Mr Singer, who was discussing the aftermath of the major cyberattack on Sony Pictures allegedly by North Korea in November 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s a lot more effective to focus on preventing and being resilient to the attacks then focussing on the clean up afterwards… The same argument can be said about fire or theft in general. If people think their way out of this is to hire crisis management or good PR they are setting themselves up for a world of hurt.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sony hack cost the studio tens of millions of US dollars, revealed the personal information of tens of thousands of people, exposed embarrassing email exchanges between high-powered actors and executives, and one top executive lost her job, reported CNBC one year later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VNXeBZuo8eM&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VNXeBZuo8eM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/baseline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/baseline/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;baseline-methodology-assessment-and-audit&#34;&gt;BASELINE METHODOLOGY ASSESSMENT AND AUDIT&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Main-Operation-Centre1024x845.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cyber-security-risk-mitigation-advanced-threat-solutions&#34;&gt;Cyber Security, Risk Mitigation &amp;amp; Advanced Threat Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited’s advanced Baseline Methodology Assessment &amp;amp; Audit solution has been developed after a decade of research and tests by IT Security and Risk Consultants, to achieve proven results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This unique assessment involves systematic and theoretical analysis of a company’s IT network security. It is divided into nine models to ascertain how a network would react to a cyberattack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not set out to provide solutions. Our Baseline Methodology Assessment report documents the findings of our investigation and presents recommendations and “best practices” applicable to specific areas where a company’s cyber security defences are deemed inadequate, or even non-existent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;network-to-server1024x845-1-1024x845.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;risk-model&#34;&gt;Risk Model&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discovering vulnerabilities in an IT Network is important. By following Eagle Eye Systems Asia’s methodology, it is possible to estimate the severity of the risks to a business and make an informed decision to reduce the risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early in the life cycle, security concerns may be identified in the architecture or design by using threat modelling. Thereafter, security issues using code review or penetration testing may be discovered, and sometimes after an application is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Failure to tighten cyber security defences may impact organisations in terms of: financial loss, damage to reputation, non-compliance, loss of accountability, privacy violation, loss of confidentiality, and may result in company being taken off-line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration-tests-wall-monitor1024x845.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dashboard-interactive-gauges-scorecard&#34;&gt;Dashboard: Interactive Gauges &amp;amp; Scorecard&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Scorecard is a key Baseline Methodology Assessment tool for determining a business’s vulnerability status for Cyber Security &amp;amp; Risk Mitigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An organisation is rated out of 100 points across seven vertical segments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scorecard includes an explanation of how the company’s final score has been calculated by our cyber security experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;it-network-infrastructure&#34;&gt;IT Network Infrastructure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration Tests form the foundation of the IT network assessment. The duration of these tests depends on the number of IP Addresses and internal and external attack surfaces within an IT network that a hacker may exploit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal-Cyber-Security1024x724.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;attack-surface-analysis&#34;&gt;Attack Surface Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of EES Asia’s holistic approach to assessment methodology, we review the security and defensibility of an organisation in a number of key areas, starting with an examination of both technical attack surfaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This includes the services presented; trusted ingress (inbound) traffic, and trusted egress (outgoing) traffic; and human attack surfaces, such as, corporate social media profile and employee’s social media activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modern-Workplace1024x845.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;network-systems-agility&#34;&gt;Network &amp;amp; Systems Agility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Network &amp;amp; Systems Agility focuses on an IT network’s ability to adapt to changing requirements that are not limited to the Information Security domain, but relate to commercial and organisational drivers, such as evolving business models and innovation cycles, and the changing requirements of the modern workplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An IT network’s oversight and maintenance, performance management, service level agreements, network survivability, and policy base are assessed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An agile network &amp;amp; systems model is predicated on the avoidance of “brittleness.” We use this term to refer to technical architecture or implementation that can withstand only a very limited attack prior to a failure affecting commercial operations, owing to the existence of an undefended core.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;monitors-and-binary1024x845.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;defensive-elements-layers&#34;&gt;Defensive Elements &amp;amp; Layers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defensive parameters focus on specific architectures, strategies, technologies and systems which offer a mitigation of addressable risk to meet an organisation’s requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The presence, coverage and risk mitigation capability of each component in this methodology has been configured for individual requirements, and represents a best-common-practice approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defensive Elements are the network, servers and clients, while the Defensive Layers are the perimeter, network, host, application and data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital-Fingerprint1024x845.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;identity-access-management-iam&#34;&gt;Identity Access Management (IAM)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Identity Access Management (IAM) is a framework for business processes that facilitates the management of electronic identities. The framework includes the technology needed to support identity management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IAM technology can be used to initiate, capture, record and manage user identities and their related access permissions in an automated fashion. This ensures that access privileges are granted according to one policy interpretation, and all individuals and services are properly authenticated, authorized and audited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poorly controlled IAM processes may lead to regulatory non-compliance because if the organisation is audited, management will not be able to prove that company data is not at risk of being misused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authentication examines: account policy, password policy, and the authentication model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;National-Security-Agency.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;intelligence-analytics&#34;&gt;Intelligence &amp;amp; Analytics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intelligence &amp;amp; Analytics is the process of analyzing information about situations and entities of strategic, operational or tactical importance to categorize the known and, with appropriate statements of probability, uncover future actions by those entities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The descriptions are drawn from what may only be available in the form of deliberately deceptive information. Thus, the analyst must correlate the similarities among deceptions and extract a common truth. Although, this practice is found in its purest form inside national intelligence agencies, these methods are also applicable in the fields of business or competitive intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;environment-analysis-signal-to-noise&#34;&gt;Environment Analysis: Signal to Noise&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Environment Analysis, or “Signal to Noise,” assessment is one of the most important responsibilities of the information security professional, to ensure management has the sufficient data to make well-informed business decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HK-stock-exchange1024x845.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certification Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd offers Certification of Achievement Awards for a select number of essential skills or services demanded by best practice policies and procedures within the IT industry, with the assistance of skilled and experienced industry instructors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Continuity Plans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As defined by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission in June 2014, licensed corporations are expected to “establish and maintain appropriate internal controls and risk management measures to protect your key business functions and recover them in a timely fashion in the event of operational disruptions,” the SFC states.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/it/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;it-security-awareness-training&#34;&gt;IT Security Awareness Training&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Security-Awareness-Training-Class.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ees-asia-s-security-awareness-training-teaches-staff-how-to-adapt-behaviour-to-lower-attack-risk&#34;&gt;EES Asia’s Security Awareness Training Teaches Staff How to Adapt Behaviour to Lower Attack Risk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd not only tests the effectiveness of security operations, we also offer employee awareness training programmes with the goal of aligning technology, employees and processes to collectively work towards blocking cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, high-profile cyber security breaches often occur when hackers target an organisation’s weakest link—its staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over-reliance on technology and failure to apply the human factor leaves companies exposed to attacks, leading to the loss of valuable intellectual property, reputation and eats in to the bottom line. From the IT trenches to the C-suite, the right people need to be organised in the right way to make security programmes work. Three areas that deserve the attention of the boards of directors and CEO’s are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;expertise-and-staffing&#34;&gt;Expertise and Staffing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accept that you will be compromised. A “win” in the cyber-threat environment is defined by how quickly and effectively your company is able to respond to hacks and extricate them from your IT systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This requires a significant level of manpower and expertise on a daily basis, but there is no substitute for taking such action in today’s high risk environment. A properly organised and staffed security team requires people with a variety of skills and certifications to deploy the technologies, understand the threats, determine hacker motives, fix vulnerabilities, and deflect attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“44 per cent of organisations say they are dissatisfied with investment in cyber security technology because they lack the in-house expertise to leverage it,” according to a 2015 study by the Ponemon Institute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To overcome this shortfall, many of our clients are optimizing their existing human resources by outsourcing the expertise and operations that a mature IT security strategy requires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Security leaders need these management skills to set up the appropriate processes and procedures, advocate for security requirements, and communicate risk to corporate leaders. Defensive technologies cannot be used to their full potential without highly skilled people who can transform data into actionable intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Database-Laptops-Manikins1024x685.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;leadership-and-accountability&#34;&gt;Leadership and Accountability&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Communicating cyber security priorities is no longer the job of just the IT team. It requires management to set the tone, support agreed-upon mitigation strategies, and educate their employees about the cyber security risks to understand risk tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Business enablement often trumps IT network security in the interest of going to market quickly, but only business leaders can ensure that the necessary checks and balances are established to hold management and employees accountable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;awareness-and-training&#34;&gt;Awareness and Training&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An informed and vigilant workforce is one of the most important defences against cyberattacks. Hackers know that most workers tend to be helpful and trusting, and hence execute attack strategies that exploit human vulnerabilities. Even boardroom leaders fall prey to socially engineered emails that unleash malicious cyber weapons, targeting the company’s IT network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An effective “human firewall” is dependent on a culture of vigilance for changing user behaviour to mitigate the risk of attack. The best employee training programmes simulate real-world hackers and provide on-the-spot training when employees fall victim to cybercrime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Board-Meeting-Black-White1024x865.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cybercrime-is-a-business-risk-hackers-hunt-for-intellectual-property-business-critical-assets&#34;&gt;Cybercrime is a business risk: Hackers hunt for intellectual property, business critical assets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cybercrime causes “enormous damage” that “not only relates to financial loss but can also lead to long-term and often systemic issues, such as, damage to brands and reputations,” says Kris McConkey, Leader for Cyber Incident Response and Threat Intelligence, in this video produced by PwC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cybercrime is a truly global phenomenon with all geographies being affected. Over a quarter of our survey respondents suffered some sort of incident, and many of those who claimed to have escaped probably did not. They are just not aware of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cybercrime is permeating every industry, even those who thought themselves immune in the past.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, the hackers were keen to steal cash and credit card information, now they are also interested in acquiring intellectual property and other business critical assets, Mr McConkey asserts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4rAQv9-EEH8&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4rAQv9-EEH8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/pentest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pentest/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;penetration-tests&#34;&gt;PENETRATION TESTS&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration-Test-Arrow-Walls1024x405.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;penetration-tests-intrusion&#34;&gt;Penetration Tests &amp;amp; Intrusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration Testing is the practice of testing a computer system, IT network or Web applications to find vulnerabilities that a hacker could exploit to gain, for example, unauthorized access to an organisation’s data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd conducts Penetration Tests as an integral part of its Baseline Methodology Assessment for Cyber Security &amp;amp; Risk Mitigation, although, it can be provided as a standalone service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration testing is conducted at a skill level higher than that of the general Internet user. Our cyber security experts use a combination of industry testing products and our own methodology to determine vulnerabilities and the defence capabilities of an IT network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other main objectives of penetration testing are to determine an organisation’s ability to identify and respond to security breaches, and test for security policy compliance and employees’ security awareness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The penetration test results are then reported back to the client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;penetration-test-Security-Breach1024x832.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;coverage-impact-testing&#34;&gt;&amp;lsquo;Coverage&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp; &amp;lsquo;Impact&amp;rsquo; Testing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The process involves gathering information about the target company before the penetration test is carried out (reconnaissance), identifying possible entry points, and simulating a hostile attempt to break into an IT network, either virtually or for real, as part of ‘Coverage’ and ‘Impact’ testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EES Asia advocates ‘Impact’ testing as an alternative to the standard ‘Coverage’ penetration test, and whilst the ‘Coverage’ test is no less important, the ‘Impact’ test has a far greater reach and replicates a real-life scenario where a company is open to attack in their normal business operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All tests are conducted under controlled conditions in accordance with the recommendations outlined in the National Institute of Standards and Technology under the US Department of Commerce, NIST SP 800-1151.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration-Testing1024x845.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dashboard-interactive-gauges-scorecard&#34;&gt;Dashboard: Interactive Gauges &amp;amp; Scorecard&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Scorecard is a key Baseline Methodology Assessment tool for determining a business’s vulnerability status for Cyber Security &amp;amp; Risk Mitigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An organisation is rated out of 100 points across seven vertical segments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scorecard includes an explanation of how the company’s final score has been calculated by our cyber security experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;certification&#34;&gt;Certification&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd offers Certification of Achievement Awards for a select number of essential skills or services demanded by best practice policies and procedures within the IT industry, with the assistance of skilled and experienced industry instructors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pen-Test-Infographic1024x845.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;social-engineering&#34;&gt;Social Engineering&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hard core aspect of the penetration tests is “Social Engineering.” It is deployed to uncover employee passwords by tracing their activity online and on social media networks, to find out personal information, such as, the names of their children, birthdates and pet names—all of which are commonly used in passwords. Likewise, a hacker could work out their passwords to break into a company’s IT network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Social Engineering” is defined as any act that influences people to respond in a way that is not in their best interest, using psychological, physiological and technological techniques, and often with malicious intent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social engineering tactics are considered to be the “greatest risk to information security,” states Social-Engineer.org on its website, whose infographic shows the top three methodologies of malicious social engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/press/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ees-asia-launches-online-platform-to-share-cyber-security-white-papers-industry-news-advice&#34;&gt;EES Asia launches online platform to share cyber security white papers, industry news &amp;amp; advice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[HONG KONG 12 March 2016] EAGLE EYE SYSTEMS (EES) ASIA Ltd has launched a new website to serve as an online platform for sharing IT security industry news, trends and concern topics, white papers, and independent expert advice to help educate enterprises and their employees about cyber security and how to prevent attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The idea is to point people in the right direction to expert information and independent reports that they may overlook as they may not be aware of the reputable sources of information available online because they lack  a deep understanding of the IT security industry,” said Sunil Rathour, CEO, Eagle Eye Securities (EES) Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.webeyesystems.com/ees-asia-launches-online-platform-to-share-cyber-security-white-papers-industry-news-advice/&#34;&gt;http://www.webeyesystems.com/ees-asia-launches-online-platform-to-share-cyber-security-white-papers-industry-news-advice/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penetration-Testing1024x845-2.png&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/security/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;security-incident-response&#34;&gt;SECURITY INCIDENT RESPONSE&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Security-Incident-Response-Help-Button1023x482.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;security-incident-response-1&#34;&gt;Security Incident Response&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Security Incident Response at Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd involves the monitoring and detection of security violations on a computer or IT network, and the execution of appropriate and immediate responses to emergencies by our dedicated &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; Response Team, who follow best practice policies and procedures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EES Asia has an all-encompassing IT security recovery strategy and action plan to create a full picture of the circumstances surrounding the cyberattack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our cyber security experts will locate the compromised computers and accounts, pinpoint the actual data accessed or stolen, and determine whether any third-party, such as customers or business partners, was also affected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computer Security Incident Management is a specialized form of Security Incident Response that aims to develop a predictable response to damaging events and computer intrusions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key areas of Security Incident Response are: Incident Recognition; Initial Incident Response; Active Defence; Forensic Protection; Incident Relations; Quarantine Triage; Investigatory Participation; Business Continuity; Disaster Recovery; and Re-Homing Preparations to move public folders from infected or hacked file, database and email servers, to “clean” servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Security-Incident-Response-Protect-Data-Key1024x845.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;four-members-of-alleged-securities-fraud-scheme-tied-to-cyber-hack-of-jp-morgan-arrested-in-us-israel&#34;&gt;Four members of alleged securities fraud scheme tied to cyber hack of JP Morgan arrested in US, Israel&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;US law enforcement authorities have arrested four people in Israel and Florida in connection with a “complex securities fraud scheme” tied to the computer hacks at JP Morgan Chase and other financial institutions, reported Bloomberg in a breaking news TV report in July 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Officials say a fifth person remains at large and the arrests are the culmination of a months-long investigation of several friends who met more than a decade ago at Florida state university, and are linked by an FBI memo to one of the largest US bank hacks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The presenter likened the case to a, “Modern computer crime. Two former college buddies (linked) to a multi-layered criminal organisation with tentacles reaching Moscow, Tel Aviv and West Palm Beach.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg News reporter, Keri Geiger, said from New York, “It appears to be a criminal enterprise. The people arrested today were not arrested for the hack of JP Morgan. Some of them were arrested for setting up a “pump and dump” scheme (of low volume, penny stocks) with the aid of information related, or linked, to various hacks, and going in, getting information from banks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier a US government spokesman announced at a press conference that hackers stole US$83 million from JPMorgan Chase and data from 100 million customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The charges involve cyber intrusions over several years, targeting 12 different companies, seven financial institutions, two financial news publications, two software development firms and a market risk intelligence company,” the spokesman said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Defendants allegedly stole personal information from over 100 million customers, including 83 million customers from one bank alone. The single largest theft of customer data from a US financial institution ever. That bank was JP Morgan Chase, and it has disclosed itself.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The spokesman added, “Sophisticated hacking to steal material non-public information is something the defendants allegedly discussed for the next stage of their sprawling criminal enterprise.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/PU4mq0qbto0&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/PU4mq0qbto0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/soc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/soc/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;security-operations-network-operations-centre&#34;&gt;Security Operations &amp;amp; Network Operations Centre&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;European-Space-Agency-Control-Centra1024x422-1.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;security-network-operations-centre-soc-noc&#34;&gt;Security &amp;amp; Network Operations Centre (SOC/NOC)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; monitoring is a major focus of Eagle Eye Systems Asia Ltd’s Information Security Operations Centre (SOC) and Network Operations Centre (NOC). The two facets complement each other and work in tandem. Together, the centre monitors, assesses and defends the enterprise’s entire information system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the sensitive nature of IT environments, we offer active, passive and host-­based technologies to specifically match the requirements of every IT network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NOC is responsible for monitoring and maintaining the overall network infrastructure. Its primary function is to ensure uninterrupted network service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;soc-noc-monitors-1024x640.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;soc&#34;&gt;SOC&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role of the SOC is to protect networks, as well as, web sites, applications, databases, servers and data centres, among other technologies and endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOC is related to the people, processes and technologies involved in providing situational awareness through the detection, containment, and remediation of IT threats. A SOC manages incidents for the enterprise, ensuring they are properly identified, analyzed, communicated, actioned/defended, investigated and reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SOC also monitors applications to identify a possible cyberattack or intrusion (event) and determine if it is a real and malicious threat (incident), and if it could have a business impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EES Asia has processes and procedures built into our SOC to clearly spell out the roles, responsibilities and monitoring procedures. They cover business, technology, operational and analytical processes. We lay out the steps to be taken in the event of an security alert or breach, such as escalation, reporting and breach response procedures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOC-NO-Server-Monitor1024x837.png&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hack-of-toy-maker-vtech-exposes-5-million-accounts-kids-photos-chats&#34;&gt;Hack of toy maker VTech exposes 5 million accounts, kids’ photos &amp;amp; chats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cyber hackers could find out the names, birthdays and where children with a VTech learning toy live, after the popular toy maker was hacked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VTech said in a statement the hackers, “Exposed the names, emails, passwords, mailing addresses and download history for five million accounts. But it goes way beyond that. The hacker was also able to pull up the photos taken of kids and the parents, along with chats and audio recordings made with the kid connect service.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It appears VTech did not do enough to encrypt customer data and passwords to guard it from hackers,” said American Technology Journalist and host of the CNET update, Bridget Carey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She continues, ”When you have company as big as VTech not doing the basics when it comes to security and protecting your data it should show you we have a huge cybersecurity problem on our hands. Companies need to invest in security before they get hacked not after.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j8aD_AWQXsQ&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j8aD_AWQXsQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/terms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;terms-and-conditions&#34;&gt;Terms and Conditions&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited’s relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term ‘Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is: 6th Floor, Cyberport 3E, Telegraph Bay, Hong Kong. Our company registration number is: 2263340, registered in Hong Kong. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This website uses cookies to monitor browsing preferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as
to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability
of the information and materials found or offered on this website for
any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and
materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude
liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent
permitted by law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely
at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your
own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or
information available through this website meet your specific
requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us.
This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout,
look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than
in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these
terms and conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property
of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages
and/or be a criminal offence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From time to time, this website may also include links to other
websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide
further information. They do not signify that we endorse the
website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked
website(s).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of
the website is subject to the laws of HK SAR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;website-privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Website Privacy Policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This privacy policy sets out how Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited uses and protects any information that you give Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited when you use this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 5 June 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we collect&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may collect the following information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;name and job title&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contact information including email address&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we do with the information we gather&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internal record keeping.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We may use the information to improve our products and services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We may periodically send promotional emails about new products,
special offers or other information which we think you may find
interesting using the email address which you have provided.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you
for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax
or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we use cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links to other websites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Controlling your personal information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the
box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the
information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information
for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time
by writing to or emailing us at: sunilrathour@eagleyesystems.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to: Sunil Rathour, Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited, 6th Floor, Cyberport 3E, Telegraph Bay, Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;website-disclaimer&#34;&gt;Website Disclaimer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Eagle Eye Systems Asia Limited takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/whitepapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/whitepapers/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;corporate-counsel-departments-are-urged-to-prepare-for-inevitable-cyber-attacks-in-alm-legal-intelligence-study&#34;&gt;Corporate counsel departments are urged to prepare for “inevitable” cyber attacks in ALM Legal Intelligence study&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of big companies have been hacked and may not even be aware of the breach that is estimated to cost on average US$6.5 million, while the pay outs have accumulated to billions of US dollars since 2014, including Anthem at between $100 million and $16 billion, and JPMorgan Chase at $1 billion dollars, according to US federal authorities and cyber security experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Faced with an uptick in cyber security attacks and potential costs, corporations and their legal departments are starting to heighten preventive awareness and improve detection after being hacked, says a research paper by three senior analysts at ALM Legal Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Meeting the threat necessitates involving legal departments more deeply in the formation of policy and process from the outset. Cyber security challenges are explored in depth in this research, including an overview of the current state of the cyber security landscape, the role of in-house counsel, company benchmarks, and analysis of where industries appear to be headed to meet current and impending threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This research reveals why cyber security matters to each and every company and the ways companies and corporate counsel departments can prepare for and react to inevitable cyber attacks,” the authors of the research paper warn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sans.org/reading-room/whitepapers/analyst/who-what-where-when-effective-threat-hunting-36785&#34;&gt;https://www.sans.org/reading-room/whitepapers/analyst/who-what-where-when-effective-threat-hunting-36785&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Law-Hammer-and-Book1024x683-1.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;prevention-systems-alone-are-insufficient-to-combat-hard-core-hacks-sans-whitepaper&#34;&gt;Prevention systems alone are insufficient to combat hard-core hacks: SANS Whitepaper&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The chances are very high that hidden threats are already in your organisation’s networks. Organisations can’t afford to believe that their security measures are perfect and impenetrable, no matter how thorough their security precautions might be,” according to a SANS Institute Whitepaper by Robert M. Lee and Rob Lee, entitled, ‘The Who, What, Where, When, Why and How of Effective Threat Hunting.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Having a perimeter and defending it are not enough because the perimeter has faded away as new technologies and interconnected devices have emerged. Prevention systems alone are insufficient to counter focused human adversaries who know how to get around most security and monitoring tools by, for example, making their attacks look like normal activity,” the authors of the Whitepaper state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Prevention systems and tools help reduce opportunities for adversaries and enable analysts to operate more effectively. The key, however, is to constantly look for attacks that get past security systems and to catch intrusions in progress rather than after attackers have completed their objectives and done worse damage to the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This process is referred to as “cyber threat hunting.” Many organisations today do some type of formal or informal hunting. For example, rather than waiting for the “you’ve been breached” notification, they are intermittently or constantly searching through their own networks for evidence of threat activity.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.infinitespada.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Infinite-Spada-Cybersecurity-and-Corporate-Counsel_Ignorance-is-Risk.pdf&#34;&gt;http://www.infinitespada.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Infinite-Spada-Cybersecurity-and-Corporate-Counsel_Ignorance-is-Risk.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cyber-Threat-Hunting-SANS-Institute-Whitepaper-Resources1024x683.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;four-approaches-to-critical-incident-response-selecting-the-best-fit-solutionary-whitepaper&#34;&gt;Four Approaches to Critical Incident Response: Selecting the Best Fit: Solutionary Whitepaper&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even those in the security business know preventive security measures are not enough to stop malware infiltrations and other security threats completely, according to a whitepaper produced by Solutionary, an NTT Group Security Company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s only a matter of when not if an organisation is breached in some manner. A data breach, a malware outbreak, a successful hacker infiltration, a DDoS attack…many have experience trying to slay one of these cyber dragons, while others have yet to deal with one, or may not even know they’ve suffered from an incident,” the authors of the executive brief highlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When calculating security spending, most organisations emphasize security controls to a much greater extent than monitoring and incident response. Bringing more balance to this spending ratio and a more proactive approach to critical incident response could mean the difference between crippling after-effects of a breach and a manageable effort to thwart attacks and properly investigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Taking a proactive approach to incident response can drastically improve an organisation’s security posture. Security frameworks and some compliance mandates also require organisations to have a security programme and an incident response plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“While every enterprise may strive for a mature incident response plan backed by a skilled security operations team, this is not a realistic goal for many organisations. Is it possible to still identify, contain and mitigate an attack without the most robust incident response plan and team in place? Yes, to a degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Successful incident response largely depends on creating a customized incident response plan that is realistic and manageable, then training and preparing employees and practicing the steps outlined in the plan.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whitepaper briefly outlines four approaches to help an organisation determine its incident response capabilities and recommends measures to implement to be best prepared to contend with a security breach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.solutionary.com/_assets/pdf/white-papers/critical-incident-repsonse-executive-brief.pdf&#34;&gt;https://www.solutionary.com/_assets/pdf/white-papers/critical-incident-repsonse-executive-brief.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Malware-Warning1024x819.jpg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;legal-sector-plays-catch-up-in-understanding-implementing-corporate-cyber-security-imperative-alm-legal-intelligence&#34;&gt;Legal sector plays “catch-up” in understanding, implementing corporate cyber security imperative: ALM Legal Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Confronted with an uptick in cyber attacks and the increasing demands of their clients, law firms are scrambling to come to terms with an evolving cybersecurity landscape that not only poses an unprecedented, existential threat to the confidentiality and trust inherent in the attorney-client relationship, but also presents new revenue opportunities for the practice of law around issues related to data, privacy and information security.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nearly 10 per cent of firms have not performed a formal information, security and privacy assessment. Approximately one-third of firms do not hold cyber liability insurance policies. More than 55 per cent of firms have either already established a cybersecurity practice or have plans to form one,” according to a research report by ALM Legal Intelligence, entitled, ‘Cybersecurity and Law Firms: Ignorance Is Risk.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Overall, the report presents a picture of an industry trying to play catch-up in understanding both the risks and opportunities presented by corporate cybersecurity imperatives,” conclude the authors of the study: Senior Analysts Steven Kovalan, Daniella Isaacson and Nicholas Bruch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As the report also details, law firms that invest in building credible expertise in cybersecurity have an opportunity to gain competitive advantage — but the window for capitalizing on this burgeoning new area of the law is closing quickly.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing from the results of the inaugural ALM Legal Intelligence Law Firm Cybersecurity Survey, the report consists of three sections: Law Firms and the Cyber Threat Environment: An Overview;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fulfilling Due Care and Pursuing Best Practices; and Cyber Opportunity, Data, Privacy and Information Security as a Practice Area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the report contains a set of tools that introduces cybersecurity best practices, overviews the current regulatory environment, and lists cybersecurity trends to monitor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.infinitespada.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Infinite-Spada-Cybersecurity-and-Law-Firms_Ignorance-is-Risk.pdf&#34;&gt;http://www.infinitespada.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Infinite-Spada-Cybersecurity-and-Law-Firms_Ignorance-is-Risk.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Law-Court-Resources-Whitepaper1024x768.jpg&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>